Finding Aid for WUOM Records, 1914-1982
Bentley Historical Library, University of Michigan
- Audio Material 1930s-1970s
  - Sound Reels (7-inch)
    - WUOM: Original Productions
      - [Tribute to] Waldo Abbot [documentary] / E.G. Burrows, et al. November 18, 1964, [R42A] (Box 18)
        (dubbed in recordings of Bob Ufer, Donn Chown, Waldo Abbot, etc. Traces history of University of Michigan Broadcasting Service and WUOM, 1950-1960 (Partial transcript in WUOM paper record series)
      - "Union Voices" [documentary] / Daniel R. Fusfeld, host, recorded 1964-1965., 13 reels 2 programs/reel
        (Musical anthology of the American labor movement.
        - Program #1: Beginnings, broadcast January 13, 1965, [R43A] (Box 18)
        - Program #2: Evangelical Songs, broadcast January 20, 1965, [R43A] (Box 18)
        - Program #3: Why Join? pt. 1, broadcast January 27, 1965, [R44A] (Box 18)
        - Program #4: Why Join? pt. 2, broadcast February 3, 1965, [R44A] (Box 18)
        - Program #5: The Anthracite Coal Strike of 1902 broadcast February 10, 1965, [R45A] (Box 18)
        - Program #6: The I.W.W. [International Workers of the World], pt. 1., broadcast February 17, 1965, [R45A] (Box 18)
        - Program #7: The I.W.W., pt. 2., broadcast February 24, 1965, [R46A] (Box 18)
        - Program #8: The I.W.W., pt. 3, broadcast March 3, 1965., [R46A] (Box 18)
        - Program #9: Heritage of Violence, pt. 1, broadcast March 10, 1965, [R47A] (Box 18)
        - Program #10: Heritage of Violence, pt. 2, broadcast March 17, 1965, [R47A] (Box 18)
        - Program #11: The Meaning of Song to Workers, broadcast March 24, 1965, [R48A] (Box 18)
        - Program #12: The Coal Miners, pt. 1, broadcast March 31, 1965, [R48A] (Box 18)
        - Program #13: The Coal Miners, pt. 2, broadcast April 7, 1965, [R49A] (Box 18)
        - Program #14: The Coal Miners, pt. 3, broadcast April 14, 1965, [R49A] (Box 18)
        - Program #15: Girl of Constant Sorrow, pt. 1, broadcast April 21, 1965 (Box 18)
        - Program #16: Girl of Constant Sorrow, pt 2., broadcast April 28, 1965, [R50A] (Box 18)
        - Program #17: The Textile Workers, pt. 1., broadcast May 5, 1965 (Box 18)
        - Program #18: The Textile Workers, pt. 2., broadcast May 12, 1965, [R51A] (Box 18)
        - Program #19: Communism in the Labor Movement, broadcast May 19, 1965, [R52A] (Box 18)
        - Program #20: Women in the Labor Movement, broadcast May 26, 1965, [R52A] (Box 18)
        - Program #21: The 1930s pt. 1., broadcast June 1. 1965, [R53A] (Box 18)
        - Program #22: The 1930s pt. 2., broadcast June 8. 1965, [R53A] (Box 18)
        - Program #23: The 1930s pt. 3., broadcast June 15, 1965, [R54A] (Box 18)
        - Program #24: Songs of Political Action, pt. 1, broadcast June 22, 1965, [R54A] (Box 18)
        - Program #25: Songs of Political Action, pt. 2, broadcast June 29, 1965, [R55A] (Box 18)
        - Program #26: Automation, broadcast July 6, 1965, [R55A] (Box 18)
      - "About Books" [interview] E.G. Burrows, host; broadcast October 1948-March 1964, 7 reels retained
        (broadcast during academic year only)
        - Interview with John Wain (American poet) March 18, 1959, [R56A] (Box 18)
        - Interview with X.J. Kennedy (American poet, University of Michigan Department of English) January 3, 1962, [R57A] (Box 18)
        - Interview with Denise Levertov (American poet) April 30, 1962, [R58A] (Box 18)
        - Interview with Samuel A. Graham (economic zoologist, University of Michigan) October 11, 1963 (Box 18)
        - November 12, 1963 Interview with Robert Bly (American poet), [R59A] (Box 18)
        - Interview with Viktor Frankl "Death Camp to Existentialism" 1963/64, [R60A] (Box 18)
        - Interview with Langston Hughes (African-American poet) undated, [R61A] (Box 18)
      - "Background," 1958-1990, 9 reels retained
        (interview/panel discussion. broadcast 1958-1990. In the 1980s Background adopted a news journal format.)
        - "Abortion: A Legal or Medical Problem?" / Andrew S. Watson; Richard D. Judge; J. R. Julen August 1, 1962, [R62A] (Box 18)
        - "The American Woman: Her Education, Her Family, Her Career" Louise Cain; Gretchen [Grothe?]; Hope Davis; Deborah Friedman; Helen Tanner December 18, 1963, [R63A] (Box 18)
        - "The Feminine Mystique" / Betty Friedan; Shirley Mattern Smith [check date: Log 07/20/1965, May 28, 1964, [R64A] (Box 18)
        - "The Peace Corps and the University of Michigan" / Harlan Hatcher; Sargent Shriver; et al. circa November 12, 1964:, [R65A] (Box 18)
        - [Panel discussion about the October 1965 sit-in at the Ann Arbor Draft Board and resultant draft status reclassification and legal suit] / Paul Kuyper; Philip Hart; et al.; Fred Hindley, announcer, March 9, 1966, [R66A] (Box 18)
      - "Classified Research at the University of Michigan" pt. 1 [panel discussion] / Gordon J. Van Wylen; Walden Rhines; A. Geoffrey Norman; Richard Mann; Roger Rapaport; Eric Chester, recorded October 27, 1967, October 31, 1967, [R67A]
        - "Classified Research at the University of Michigan" pt. 2 [panel discussion] November 7, 1967, [R68A] (Box 18)
        - ["Student Radicalism"] / Stanley M. Swinton; Michael Dann; Roger Rappaport December 31, 1967, [R69A] (Box 18)
        - [5 students reply to Lyndon B Johnson's State of the Union address], broadcast Special of the Week, January 23, 1968, [R70A] (Box 18)
      - "Commentary," 1961 (Box 19)
        (viewpoints on topics of contemporary interest presented by University of Michigan faculty], broadcast October 1954-? Preceded by regular news commentary program featuring Preston Slosson. 1 reel retained)
        - [Preston Slosson's final program] Analysis and summary of critical world issues as they might be viewed from the White House August 21, 1961, [R71A] (Box 19)
      - "Conservation Report" [interview/news digest] broadcast October 1956-October 1972
        (2 reels retained (2 programs per reel))
        - "Action by Citizens Groups a Way to Guard Local Water Needs" / Lyle Crane (University of Michigan Department of Conservation) October 2, 1962, [R72A] (Box 19)
        - "Lumber Quality Begins in the Woods" / John Carow (University of Michigan Department of Forestry) October 16, 1962, [R72A] (Box 19)
        - "Michigan Produces Rich Variety of Christmas Trees" / Kenneth P. Davis (University of Michigan Department of Forestry) November 27, 1962, [R73A] (Box 19)
        - "Deer Still Need Management" / A.B. Cowan (University of Michigan Department of Wildlife) December 4, 1962, [R73A] (Box 19)
      - "Eleventh Hour" [arts interview] / E.G. Burrows, host, broadcast January 1968-September 1982
        (3 reels retained)
        - "Ragtime, Tin Pan Alley, and the University of Michigan Varsity Show" / Gerald Marks discusses and sings works of Seymor Simons and other University of Michigan alumni with popular music careers February 13, 1968, [R74A] (Box 19)
        - North Campus Interview: U-M School of Music rehearsal for upcoming "Contemporary Directions" concert / George Wilson; Sydney Hodkinson; et al. February 24, 1968, [R75A] (Box 19)
        - Interview with Joyce Carol Oates May 16, 1968, [R76A] (Box 19)
      - "Especially for Women" [interview/panel discussion], broadcast October 1949-July 1951
        (1 reel retained)
        (succeeded by Guest of Honor, broadcast September 1951-October 1952)
        - January 30, 1950 Eleanor Roosevelt, Marie Miller, Waldo Abbot, [R77A] (Box 19)
        - Dorothy Thompson; [____] Baldwin; et al. In conjunction with University of Michigan Religion in Life Week undated, [R77A] (Box 19)
      - "Hello, Alumni" [report/interview/documentary] / T. Hawley Tapping, host, 13 reels retained
        (broadcast October 1948-November 1954 (academic year only))
        - Rose Bowl 1950 / Bill Fleming; Bob Ufer; Don Dufek; et al., January 15, 1951 (Box 19)
          (Comments from fans and team members; letters from alumni; excerpts from press coverage nationwide)
        - Willie Heston November 23, 1951, 15 ips; [R78A] (Box 19)
        - Alexander G. Ruthven January 14, 1954, 15 ips; [R79A] (Box 19)
        - Henry Sanders January 19, 1954, 15 ips; [R80A] (Box 19)
        - John L. Brumm January 21, 1954, 15 ips; [R81A] (Box 19)
        - [___] Durfee January 25, 1954, 15 ips; [R82A] (Box 19)
        - Guest: C.O. Wisle, January 26, 1954r, 15 ips; [R83A] (Box 19)
        - James B. Edmondson January 28, 1954, 15 ips; [R84A] (Box 19)
        - Philip Bursley January 29, 1954, 15 ips; [R85A] (Box 19)
        - [____] Robbins March 18, 1954, 15 ips; [R86A] (Box 19)
        - Matt Mann March 21, 1954, 15 ips; [R87A] (Box 19)
        - March 22, 1954 S.T. Dana, 15 ips; [R88A] (Box 19)
        - [Anthology]: Voice of Yost / Fred J. Lawton; Hello, Alumni #2 / Bob Morgan, undated, 15 ips; [R88A] (Box 19)
      - "I Open the Door" [readings of children's literature] / Virginia Michalak, reader, 1964., 2 reels retained
        (broadcast October 1963-April 1966 during academic year only)
        - "The Green Christmas" from Henry Huggins recorded September 17, 1964: original broadcast December 2, 1963, [R90A] (Box 19)
        - Excerpt from The Hobbitt original broadcast December 9, 1963 (Box 19)
        - "The Man with the Red Eyes" from A Wrinkle in Time, recorded October 6, 1964, [R91A] (Box 19)
          (original broadcast October 26, 1964)
      - "Record Collector" [music anthology] / Warren Good, host, 1 reel retained
        (broadcast November 1949-September 1975.)
        - Christmas Show December 23, 1960, [R92A] (Box 19)
      - "Special of the Week" [speech/panel discussion]
        (broadcast November 1961-[August] 1973. 2 reels retained. Most programs originated in Washington, D.C. and were distributed by the National Association for Educational Broadcasting network.)
        - Speech commemorating the fifth anniversary of the Peace Corps / Jack Hood Vaughn March 2, 1966, [R93A] (Box 19)
        - Speech re: Black Nationalism / Albert Cleague; Session of America in Crisis Teach-In (University of Michigan) October 5, 1967, [R94A] (Box 19)
    - U-M Ceremonies and Convocations
      University of Michigan: Ceremonies and Convocations. Recordings of various ceremonial events, including building dedications. In general, though WUOM regularly broadcasts the university commencement exercises, these recordings, along with recordings of Honors Convocation, are kept only when transcripts of the addresses are not yet available.
      WUOM: Broadcast Programs subseries includes representative recordings of regularly broadcast programs originating with WUOM, often featuring University of Michigan administrators and faculty.
      - Birthday Dinner Ceremonies Honoring Alexander Grant Ruthven / Ruthven; Harlan H. Hatcher; Frank [Whitman?], master of ceremonies, recorded June 14, 1962, [R95A] (Box 19)
      - Commencement 1961 / address by Edward R. Murrow, June 17, 1961, 2 reels; [R96A-R97A] (Box 19)
        (Audition copy available in Box 16)
      - Commencement 1963 / address by C.P. Snow. June 8, 1963, [R98A] (Box 19)
      - Dedication Ceremony: Chrysler Center / Harlan H. Hatcher; Lynn Townsend; Harry Chesbrough; Gordon J. Van Wylen November 29, 1967, [R99A] (Box 19)
      - Dedication Ceremony: Federal Mogul Building / Harlan H. Hatcher; George Romney; et. al. February 26, 1963, [R100A] (Box 19)
      - Dedication Ceremony: Kresge Hearing Research Institute / William N. Hubbard; H. Vaughn Whitehead; Harlan H. Hatcher; et al. May 20, 1963, [R101A] (Box 19)
      - Dedication Ceremony: Law School Television / Allan Smith; John Satterfield; et al. January 12, 1961, [R102A] (Box 19)
      - Dedication Ceremony: Matthai Botanical Gardens / Harlan H. Hatcher; Frederick C. Matthai; William C. Steere; A. Geoffrey Norman; speakers June 14, 1962, [R103A] (Box 19)
      - Dedication Ceremony: Towsley Center for Continuing Medical Education / Robben W. Fleming; Harry A. Towsley; et al., [March 27, 1969], 2 reels; [R104A-R105A] (Box 19)
      - Dedication Ceremony: University Events Building [Crisler Arena] / Bill Fleming; Donald F. Tucker; Marcus Plant; Bob Brown; Fritz Crisler; Robben W. Fleming February 27, 1968, [R106A] (Box 20)
      - Special Student Convocation: Participation and Responsibility / Harlan H. Hatcher March 18, 1965, 2 reels; [R107A-R108A] (Box 20)
        (addresses student activism)
    - U-M Conferences and Lectures
      University of Michigan: Conferences and Lectures. Representative recordings of lectures, panel discussions, etc., presented on campus both by members of the university community and by figures of national and international reputation. When known, the recordings in this unit are arranged first by conference name or sponsoring organization, then alphabetically by title.
      - Alumni University
        - "Today's Graduate Student" / Stephen H. Spurr, recorded April 29, 1965 broadcast Lecture Hour, August 19, 1965, [R109A] (Box 20)
      - Creative Arts Festival
        - Poetry Reading / W.D. Snodgrass; introduction by Donald Hall, recorded May 10, 1963, [R110A] (Box 20)
      - Poetry Reading / James Dickey; introduction by Donald Hall, recorded May 13, 1963 broadcast Lecture Hour, June 26, 1963, [R111A] (Box 20)
      - Poetry Reading / John Berryman, recorded March 21, 1965, 2 reels; [R112A-R113A] (Box 20)
      - Poetry Reading / Radcliffe Squires--recorded March 25, 1965 broadcast Lecture Hour, September 16, 1965, [R114A] (Box 20)
      - Department of English (Box 20)
      - Poetry Reading / Galway Kinnell, recorded April 12, 1961 broadcast Lecture Hour, May 22, 1961, [R115A] (Box 20)
      - College of Literature, Science, and the Arts
        - Afro-American: A Survey History [pilot course, Afro-American Studies Program] / Harold Cruse, et al., broadcast Fall 1969, 12 reels; [R116A-R127A] (Box 20)
      - Student Legal Defense Committee
        - Reclassification Rally [panel discussion]: "Dissent and Draft" / Irene Murphy; Ross Wilhelm; Philip Hart, recorded April 1, 1966, [R128A] (Box 20)
      - Unidentified Sponsorship
        - [Poetry reading] / Donald Hall [undatd], [R129A] (Box 20)
        - [Press conference with Robert Frost], recorded April 2, 1962, [R130A] (Box 20)
        - "The University as an Elite Institution" / Arthur Eastman, recorded May 18, 1962, [R131A] (Box 20)
      - University of Michigan Alumni Association
        - "Life and Service of Gabriel Richard" / Edward J. Hickey, recorded October 20, 1967, [R132A] (Box 20)
          (broadcast Lecture Hour December 2, 1967)
      - Vietnam "Action" Teach-In
        - Speeches and panel discussion / Robert Sklar; Howard Zinn; Andrew Pulley; Dave Dellinger, recorded September 20, 1969, 3 reels; [R133A-R135A] (Box 20)
          (See also: Sound Reels (10.5")
      - War Moratorium (sponsor: New Mobilization to End the War)
        - "Business and the War" [panel discussion] / Robben W. Fleming; Mike Ryder; J.B. Ritchie; Stan McGlaughlin, recorded October 15, 1969, 2 reels; [R136A-R137A] (Box 20)
    - U-M History
      The University of Michigan: History subseries is composed chiefly of recordings of oral history interviews with university faculty and staff.
      - Erich Walter Talks about Harlan Hatcher [reminiscences], recorded December 27, 1961, [R138A] (Box 20)
      - Interview with T. Hawley Tapping [oral history] 1958, [R139A] (Box 20)
        (Reminiscences re: the University of Michigan; some mention of Clarence Cook Little)
    - U-M Sesquicentennial Celebration
      University of Michigan: Sesquicentennial Celebration consists of recordings of addresses, lectures, and panel discussions, as well as ceremonial events held throughout 1967 to celebrate the university's 150th anniversary.
      - $55 Million Dollar Campaign
        - Radio spots / Harlan H. Hatcher [recorded] February 28, 1967, [R140A] (Box 21)
      - University of Michigan Birthday Symposium [Alumni Weekend]
        - "The Right of Free Expression" / Arthur Miller; Fred Hindley, host, recorded March 3, 1967 Includes question-answer session, broadcast Special of the Week, [R141A] (Box 21)
          (See Also: Sound Reels (10.5")
      - Voices of Civilization Lecture Series October 2-6, 1967 (Major Ceremony IV)
        - "Race Relations" [speech] / Ralph Ellison broadcast Special of the Week, October 9, 1967, [R142A] (Box 21)
          (See Also: Sound Reels (10.5"))
        - "The Shift of Power from East to West" [speech] / Dean Acheson, recorded October 2, 1967, 3 reels; [R143A-R145A] (Box 21)
          (broadcast December 1, 1967)
    - State and Local History and Events
      The subseries State and Local History and Events includes actuality (recordings of the event) and oral history recordings pertaining both to Ann Arbor and to the State of Michigan.
      - Interview with R.E. Olds [oral history] [recorded] April 19, 1950. Development of Michigan's Auto Industry, [R146A] (Box 21)
        (also on DAT cassette)
      - John F. Kennedy Campaign Visit to Ann Arbor
        - Speech at Willow Run Airport / [___] Huizenga, announcer, WCBN October 13, 1960, [R147A] (Box 21)
        - Speeches at [Willow Run] Airport and Michigan Union; October 13, 14 1960, 15 ips; [R148A] (Box 21)
        - Farewell Speech; October 14, 1960, [R149A] (Box 21)
      - Upper Peninsula Dialect Stories / Charles Follo undated Collection of favorite "true" stories, and reminiscences of Upper Penninsula residents., [R150A] (Box 21)
  - Sound Reels (10 1/2-inch")
    - WUOM: Anniversary and Dedication Programs
      - WUOM Dedication Week Variety Show, January14 1950, [R153B] (Box 22)
        (Dedication of WUOM-FM and 25th anniversary celebration of UMBS, Robert Q. Lewis and Steve Filipiak, hosts; Ward Quaal; Bob Ufer; Mary Bell; et al., original recording January 14, 1950, dub November 16, 1964 broadcast live January 14, 1950)
      - Tenth Anniversary Program, recorded July 3, 1958, 2 reels; [R154B-R155B] (Box 22)
        (broadcast Panorama July 5, 1958 Partial script in WUOM paper records series)
    - WUOM: Original Productions
      - "The American Town: A Self-Portrait" [oral history documentary], 3 reels of 6 retained
        - Program #3: "The Copper Country" pt. 1 recorded February 16, 1966, [R156B] (Box 22)
          (broadcast April 6, 1966)
        - Program #5: Durand [MI], recorded December 16, 1964, [R158B] (Box 22)
          (broadcast March 18, 1965)
      - [Anthology of interviews], dub June 12, 1971, 3 3/4 ips; [R159B]
        - Press conference with Robben W. Fleming January 3, 1968 (Box 22)
        - Press conference with Christian Barnard March 6, 1968 (Box 22)
        - Robben W. Fleming Meeting with BAM; CBS Interview with Robben W. Fleming April 15, 1968 (Box 22)
        - First Heart Transplant, University of Michigan Hospital September 23, 1968, December 3, 1968 (Box 22)
        - Press conference with Robben W. Fleming in Traverse City [MI] July 24, 1969 (Box 22)
      - "A Dickens of A Christmas" [original dramatization based on writings of Charles Dickens] / Bert Hornback; Lord Chamberlain's Players; music by Quin Adamson, recorded December 23, 1970, [R160B] (Box 22)
        (broadcast December 24, 1970 Script in WUOM paper records series)
      - [Michigan Men in the Civil War] [documentary] / Russell E. Bidlack, 3 reels
        (Companion series to University of Michigan Summer Session 1961)
        - Program #1: The First Battle of Bull Run broadcast Panorama, July 15, 1961, [R161B] (Box 22)
        - Program #2: Prisoner of War Experiences broadcast Panorama, July 29, 1961, [R162B] (Box 22)
        - Program #3: The Lighter Side of the War broadcast Panorama, August 12, 1961, [R163B] (Box 22)
      - "The News from Dallas" [documentary] / Fred Hindley, narrator, recorded November 5, 1964, [R164B] (Box 22)
        (Partial script in WUOM paper records series)
      - News in 20th Century America [documentary] / Leland Stowe, host, 2 reels of 29 retained
        (broadcast June-October 1959)
        - Program #4: Women in Journalism / Leland Stowe; Pauline Fredericks; Sylvia Porter; et al., recorded February 5, 1959, [R165B] (Box 22)
        - Program #13: The Columnist: Pressures and Problems / Frank Angelo; Sylvia Porter; Drew Pearson, recorded April 22, 1959, [R166B] (Box 22)
      - One Nation Indivisible [award-winning documentary]--broadcast March-May 1958, 2 reels of 13 retained; 15 ips
        - Program #1: The Rise of Nationalism, broadcast March 6, 1958, [R167B] (Box 23)
        - Program #13: Internationalism, broadcast May 29, 1958, [R168B] (Box 23)
      - They Fought Alone [award-winning drama-documentary], broadcast September-December 1953, 1 reel of 13 retained; 15 ips
        (Stories based on the lives of men and women who fought for the freedom to know." Scripts available in WUOM paper records series.)
        - Program #3: Elizabeth Blackwell [first woman admitted to medical school in the United States], broadcast October 19, 1953, [R169B] (Box 23)
      - Union Sesquicentennial [sic], Documentary history of Michigan Union October 28, 1954, [R170B] (Box 23)
    - WUOM: Program Series
      - Symposium, 1973-1975., 9 reels retained
        ([monthly studio interview/public forum program on topics of interest to University of Michigan faculty, staff, students, and administrators], broadcast September 1972-April 1975 academic year only)
        - 1973
          - "The Economic Future of the University of Michigan / Robben W. Fleming; David Fowler September 24, 1973, [R171B] (Box 23)
          - "Faculty-Staff Salaries" / Allen F. Smith; Ralph Loomis October 22, 1973, [R172B] (Box 23)
          - "Women's Athletics" / Robben W. Fleming; Eunice Burns; Sheryl Szady November 19, 1973, [R173B] (Box 23)
          - "Student Government" / Robben W. Fleming; Henry Johnson; Kathleen Kolar December 21, 1973, [R174B] (Box 23)
        - 1974
          - "Fuel Shortage" / Robben W. Fleming; Dan Wendall; Dan Bluggerman January 22, 1974, [R175B] (Box 23)
          - "Technology and Education" / Robben W. Fleming; Bernard Galler February 19, 1974, [R176B] (Box 23)
          - "Student Financial Aid" / Tom Butts; Joseph Kosand March 19, 1974, [R177B] (Box 23)
          - "Unionization at University of Michigan" / Robben W. Fleming; Carl Cohen March 19, 1974, [R178B] (Box 23)
        - 1975
          - [A look at the 1975/76 academic year] / Robben W. Fleming; Frank H.T. Rhodes; Wilbur K. Pierpont, January 21,1975, [R179B] (Box 23)
    - U-M Ceremonies and Convocations
      - Award Presentation and Banquet Address (Income Maintenance and the Social Security System Conference, November 10-12, 1968) / Wilbur J. Cohen; Robben W. Fleming; et al. November 11, 1968, [R180B] (Box 23)
      - Commencement 1962 / address by Robert S. McNamara, June 12, 1962, [R181B] (Box 23)
      - Commencement 1964 / address by Lyndon B. Johnson ("The Great Society"), May 22, 196, [R182B] (Box 23)
        (Audition copy available in Box 16, also on DAT cassette)
      - Commencement 1966 / address by John Kenneth Galbraith ("Foreign Policy, Politics, and the University"), April 30, 1966, [R183B] (Box 24)
        (speech rebroadcast Lecture Hour June 30, 1966)
      - Commencement 1974 / address by Gerald R. Ford; Gerald R. Ford; Bruce Catton; Leo Goldberg; honorary degree recipients, May 4, 1974, [R184B] (Box 24)
      - Commencement [winter] 1976 / Betty Ford, Wilbur K. Pierpont, December 9, 1976, [R185B] (Box 24)
        (address broadcast Background December 21, 1976)
      - Dedication Address: Peace Corps Plaque / Harlan H. Hatcher; Harlan Cleveland; Erich Walter; clip from original Kennedy speech May 8, 1964, [R186B] (Box 24)
      - Dedication Ceremony: Bentley Historical Library (Theme: "Local History Is Alive and Well") May 2, 1974, [R187B] (Box 24)